New England Archivists, Inc. Records 1992.0012
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
New England Archivists, Inc. Records
undated, 1969-2013
1992.0012
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
38.0 Linear feet
The New England Archivists was formed in 1973. The organization is incorporated as a nonprofit organization under the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Its purpose as defined by the Bylaws is as follows: "to foster the preservation and use of records of enduring value in New England, public and private, corporate and individual, and to improve the management and public awareness and understanding of such records, by providing pre-professional and continuing education in archival theory and practices; a forum for the exchange of information among individuals and institutions having responsibility for records of enduring value in the region; and appropriate means of communication and cooperation with other archival organizations and with individual and groups of allied professions."
New England Archivists, Inc.
History
The New England Archivists was formed in 1973. The organization is incorporated as a nonprofit organization under the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Its purpose as defined by the Bylaws is as follows: "to foster the preservation and use of records of enduring value in New England, public and private, corporate and individual, and to improve the management and public awareness and understanding of such records, by providing pre-professional and continuing education in archival theory and practices; a forum for the exchange of information among individuals and institutions having responsibility for records of enduring value in the region; and appropriate means of communication and cooperation with other archival organizations and with individual and groups of allied professions."
The NEA's ongoing concerns are preserving and making available for use original documentary materials. NEA sponsors two conferences per year, one of which also serves as the annual meeting, that offer programs of interest to members of the archival community and provide a forum for group discussions and the exchange of ideas. In addition, the NEA sponsors several day-long workshops and seminars each year, which provide a thorough examination of such topics as archival security, arrangement and description, records management, preservation, and appraisal.
With membership over 600, NEA continues to offer professional support, information, and on-going training to records curators throughout the New England area.
Scope and Content
The records of the New England Archivists, Inc. contain historically significant materials which pertain to NEA's function as a professional organization for archivists in the New England area since 1973. Among the materials are records of the presidents, newsletters, committee files, and workshop data. These records provide a broad overview of the history of the organization, as well as information about its activities and programs.
Organization
Series I: Constitution and Bylaws ( 1973-1989 ) contains materials relating to the original bylaws of the organization, drawn up in l973, as well as revisions to those by-laws over the years. Corporation papers drawn up in the mid-l970s and again in the mid-l980s are also found in this series.
Series II: Officers ( 1969- ) contains the files of NEA presidents, vice presidents, secretaries, treasureres and representatives from l977 on. The series is arranged in chronological order with records of each officer as a separate subseries. The files are arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
Series III: Meetings ( 1972- ) contains materials on the annual spring and fall NEA meetings from l972 on. If they have been transferred, the Local Arrangement and Program Committee files for the meetings are also included in this series. The files are arranged chronologically.
Series IV: Committees ( 1972- ) contains the files of both ad hoc and standing committees, including: by-laws revision, education, long range planning, outreach, public relations coordinator, program, and steering. The files are arranged alphabetically by committee and chronologically therein.
Series V: Subject Files ( 1977- ) holds alphabetically arranged information on grant applications, awards, the NEA letterhead, and public relations. The materials have been collected and contributed by numerous NEA members.
Series VI: Special Format materials ( 1973-1993 ) contains audio tapes and cassettes of NEA workshops and business meetings, photos, and proclamations and official statements from New England governors concerning Archives Week.
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged in accordance with the administrative structure of the organization. Some duplication and overlap exists.
Separated Material
The NEA Newsletter has been separated from the collection and cataloged. Please consult the Libraries' online catalog, HOMER, for a complete holdings list.
Acquisition Information
The archives of the New England Archivists were initially donated by NEA to the University of Connecticut Libraries in l980. The records have been transferred to UConn in yearly accessions, from 1981 to the present.
Accruals
The most recent addition of materials was incorporated into the collection in March 2013.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a small collection of materials pertaining to New England professional organizations. Details regarding officers, meetings and acitivites of the New England Archivists can be found on the NEA Website. For additional information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
New England Archivists, Inc.; Administrative records; Archivists; Audio visual materials; Audiocassettes; Bylaws; Correspondence; Financial Records; Minutes (administrative records); Newsletters; Notes; Photocopies; Photographs; Publications
- Series I: Constitution and Bylaws, 1973-1989
  - Bylaws, l973-1978 (Box 1:1)
  - Bylaws revision, 1978 (Box 1:2)
  - Bylaws, 1985-1986 (Box 1:3)
  - Bylaws, as amended, 1989 (Box 1:4)
  - Corporation papers, 1973, 1976 (Box 1:5)
  - Incorporation, 1973 (Box 1:6)
- Series II: Officers, 1969-1997
  - Subseries A: Presidents, 1969-1997
    - William Joyce, l977-1978
      - COPACE workshop, 1975-1977 (Box 1:7)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 1:8)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 1:9)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 1:10)
      - NEA Board meetings, 1973-1979 (Box 1:11)
      - Non-profit status, 1976-1977 (Box 1:12)
      - U.S. Newspaper Project, 1977 (Box 1:13)
      - White House conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1977-1978 (Box 1:14)
      - Workshop, 1977 Fall (Box 1:15)
    - Wilma Slaight, 1978-1979
      - Auditing Committee, 1978 (Box 1:16)
      - Board meeting, 1978 June (Box 1:17)
      - Board meeting, 1978 November (Box 1:18)
      - Board meeting, 1979 January (Box 1:19)
      - Board meeting, 1979 April (Box 1:20)
      - Board meeting, 1979 June (Box 1:21)
      - Brochure, 1978 (Box 1:22)
      - Candidates, 1978 (Box 1:23)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1:24)
      - Education Committee questionnaire, 1978 (Box 1:25)
      - Memos, 1979 (Box 1:26)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 1:27)
    - Marjorie Duval, 1979-1980
      - Annual Meeting, 1980 April (Box 1:28)
      - Auditing Committee, 1979 (Box 1:29)
      - Board meeting, 1979 June (Box 1:30)
      - Board meeting, 1979 November (Box 1:31)
      - Board meeting, 1980 January (Box 1:32)
      - Board meeting, 1980 April (Box 1:33)
      - By-Laws Committee, 1980 (Box 1:34)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1:35)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1:36)
      - Education Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 1:37)
      - Logo, undated (Box 1:38)
      - NEA/ MARAC, 1979 (Box 1:39)
      - Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 1:40)
      - Nominating Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 1:41)
      - Printing and mailing, 1978-1979 (Box 1:42)
      - Program Committee, 1980 (Box 1:43)
    - John Kendall, 1980-1981
      - Amherst local history project, 1983 (Box 1:44)
      - Archives Advisory Commission: Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 1:45)
      - Archives Advisory Commission: Massachusetts, 1974-1976 (Box 1:46)
      - Archives Advisory Commission: Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Box 1:47)
      - Archives Advisory Commission: Massachusetts, 1975-1977 (Box 1:48)
      - Archives Advisory Commission: Massachusetts, 1976-1978 (Box 1:49)
      - Archives Advisory Commission: Massachusetts, 1977-1978 (Box 1:50)
      - Bay State Medical Center Project, 1988-1989 (Box 1:51)
      - Bicentennial workshops, 1969-1974 (Box 1:52)
      - Coalition to Save Our Documentary Heritage, 1981-1981 (Box 1:53)
      - Coalition to Save Our Documentary Heritage, 1983 (Box 2:54)
      - Coalition to Save Our Documentary Heritage, 1982-195 (Box 2:55)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 2:56)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 2:57)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 2:58-60)
      - Correspondence: Society of American Archivists, 1972-1980 (Box 2:61)
      - Financial Management for Associations, 1981, 1986 (Box 2:62)
      - Financial Management for Associations, 1988 (Box 2:63)
      - Legislative Activity, 1981 (Box 2:64)
      - Logo, 1985-1986 (Box 2:65)
      - National Archives and Records Administration, 1982 (Box 2:66)
      - NEA/ SAA regional, 1983 (Box 2:67)
      - National Historic Publications and Records Commission, 1973-1976 (Box 2:68)
      - National Historic Publications and Records Commission, 1981 (Box 2:69-70)
      - Public Records Committee, 1982 (Box 2:71)
      - Symposium: governmental record resources, 1972 (Box 2:72)
    - James O'Toole, 1981-1982
      - Board meeting, 1982 May (Box 2:73)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 2:74)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 2:75)
      - Meeting Notes, 1973, 1976, 1977 (Box 2:76)
      - Meeting Notes, 1981 July (Box 2:77)
      - Meeting Notes, 1981 October (Box 2:78)
      - Meeting Notes, 1982 January (Box 2:79)
      - Meeting Notes, 1982 May (Box 2:80)
      - Public Records Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 2:81)
      - Tax exempt status, 1981-1982 (Box 2:82-85)
    - Helen Samuels, 1982-1983
      - Annual meeting, 1982 Spring (Box 2:86)
      - Annual meeting, 1983 Spring (Box 2:87)
      - Archives inventory, undated (Box 2:88)
      - Board correspondence, 1983 (Box 2:89)
      - Board meetings, 1982 May (Box 2:90)
      - Board meetings, 1982 July (Box 2:91)
      - Board meetings, 1982 October (Box 3:92)
      - Board meetings, 1983 January (Box 3:93)
      - Board meetings, 1983 April (Box 3:94)
      - Board meetings, 1983 June (Box 3:95)
      - Board meetings, 1983 November (Box 3:96)
      - Board meetings, 1984 January (Box 3:97)
      - Board meetings, 1984 April (Box 3:98)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3:99)
      - Education activities, 1982-1983 (Box 3:100)
      - Education coordinator, 1983 (Box 3:101)
      - Finances, 1982-1983 (Box 3:102)
      - Hale Fund, 1983 (Box 3:103)
      - Journal, 1982-1983 (Box 3:104)
      - Lobbying, 1983 (Box 3:105)
      - MARAC/ NEA joint publication, 1981 (Box 3:106)
      - Meeting, 1982 Fall (Box 3:107)
      - Membership analysis, 1983 (Box 3:108)
      - Membership brochure, 1983 (Box 3:109)
      - Newsletter, 1982-1984 (Box 3:110)
      - NHPRC grant application, 1986 (Box 3:110a)
      - Nominating Committee, 1985 (Box 3:111)
      - OCLC Workshop, 1984 (Box 3:112)
      - Photographic Workshop, 1984 (Box 3:113)
      - Pending, 1982 (Box 3:114)
      - People to watch, 1982 (Box 3:115)
      - Public records, 1982 (Box 3:116)
      - Publicity, 1982 (Box 3:117)
      - SAA, 1983 (Box 3:118)
      - Schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 3:119)
      - Tax status, 1982-1983 (Box 3:120)
      - Treasurer's report, 1983 (Box 3:121)
    - Connell Gallagher, 1983-1984
      - Annual meeting, 1984 April (Box 3:122)
      - Annual meeting plans, 1983 May - 1984 January (Box 3:123)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3:124)
      - Executive board meetings, 1981 September - 1982 January (Box 3:125)
      - Executive board meetings, 1983 January - June (Box 3:126)
      - Executive board meetings, 1984 January (Box 3:127)
      - Executive board meetings, 1984 April (Box 3:128)
      - Executive board meetings, 1984 April (Box 3:129)
      - Fall Meeting plans, 1984 (Box 3:130)
      - Grant Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 3:131)
      - Hale Award, 1983 (Box 3:132)
      - Publication Committee, 1984 (Box 3:133)
    - Edward Galvin, 1984-1985
      - Boston City Archives, 1984-1985 (Box 3:134)
      - NEA Education Grant--Proposal, 1984 (Box 3:135)
      - NEA Education Grant--Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 3:136)
      - NEA Education Grant--Worcester meeting, 1984 (Box 3:137)
    - Randall Jimerson, 1985-1986
      - Annual meeting, 1986 April (Box 3:138)
      - Board meeting, 1985 June (Box 3:139)
      - Board meeting, 1985 October (Box 3:140)
      - Board meeting, 1986 January (Box 3:141)
      - Board meeting, 1986 April (Box 3:142)
      - Board meeting, 1986 October (Box 3:143)
      - Board meeting, 1987 January (Box 3:144)
      - Certification, 1985-1986 (Box 3:145)
      - Committees, 1985 (Box 3:146)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4:147)
      - "Documenting New England": proposed NEA book, 1984 (Box 4:148)
      - Education Coordinators, 1985-1986 (Box 4:149)
      - Education Grant, 1985-1986 (Box 4:150-151)
      - Executive Board, 1985-1986 (Box 4:152)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 1985 Fall (Box 4:153)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 1986 Spring (Box 4:154)
      - Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 4:155)
      - Membership, 1985 (Box 4:156)
      - Membership survey, 1986 (Box 4:157)
      - Minutes, 1979-1986 (Box 4:158)
      - National Coordinating Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4:159)
      - NEA banner, 1985 (Box 4:160)
      - Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 4:161)
      - Public records, 1984-1985 (Box 4:162)
      - Public relations, 1984 (Box 4:163)
      - Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 4:164)
      - Task Force on Archives and Society, 1984-1986 (Box 4:165)
      - Treasurer, 1984-1985 (Box 4:166)
      - U.S. Archivist appointment, 1986 (Box 4:167)
      - Manual - Caring for Historical Records
        - Reference, undated (Box 21:924)
        - Originals, 1988 (Box 21:925)
        - SAA Edition Master, 1990 (Box 21:926)
      - National Historical Publications and Records Commission Grant, 1988-1989
        - Proposal/Report, 1990 (Box 21:927)
        - Project reports, 1988-1990 (Box 21:928)
        - NEA brochures, undated (Box 21:929)
        - Letters of support, 1986-1989 (Box 21:930)
      - Workshop forms, handouts, outlines
        - Day 1 Exercise (Box 21:931)
        - Day 1 Discussion questions (Box 21:932)
        - Day 2 handouts (Box 21:933-934)
        - Outreach masters (Box 21:935)
        - One day workshop evaluation forms (Box 21:936)
        - Registration forms (Box 21:937)
        - Host letters and checklist (Box 21:938)
        - Day 2 evaluation form (Box 21:939)
        - Day 1 evaluation form (Box 21:940)
        - Six month evaluation form (Box 21:941)
        - Organizing manuscripts and archives workshop--Outlines and notes (Box 21:942)
        - Institutional guidelines for archives (Box 21:943)
      - NEA Meetings
        - 1989 Fall (Box 21:944)
        - 1989 Spring (Box 21:945)
        - 1988 Fall (Box 21:946)
        - NHPRC Grant aaplication, 1988-1989 (Box 21:947)
        - 1990 Spring (Box 21:948)
        - ASCH Talk, 1989 September (Box 21:949)
        - NEA Education Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 21:950)
        - NEA Education Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 21:951)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 21:952)
        - Connecticut Archivists Association (Box 21:953)
        - Connecticut Archives Group (Box 21:954)
      - Reference
        - Reports and proposals on other archival projects, 1983-1987 (Box 21:955)
        - Connecticut Education Project, 1983 (Box 21:956)
        - SAA input, 1986 (Box 21:957)
        - Information on archival education and workshops, 1988 (Box 21:958)
        - Minnesota training workshops, 1987 (Box 21:959)
      - Administrative files
        - NHPRC correspondence, 1988 (Box 21:960)
        - Reports to NHPRC, 1988-1989 (Box 21:961)
        - Grants and contracts office, 1987-1991 (Box 21:962)
        - Budget, 1987 (Box 21:963)
        - UConn Foundation transmittals, 1989 (Box 21:964)
        - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 21:965)
        - Project correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 21:966)
        - Project news releases, 1988 (Box 21:967)
        - Final report, 1990 (Box 21:968)
        - NEA Grant proposal, 1987 (Box 21:969)
        - Project publicity, 1988-1989 (Box 21:970)
        - Project brochure (Box 21:971)
      - Workshop data
        - Summaries and evaluations (Box 21:972)
        - Participants - Master (Box 21:973)
        - Day 1 evaluations (Box 21:974)
        - Day 2 evaluations (Box 21:975)
        - Six month evaluations (Box 21:976)
      - Workshops
        - Lists of participants (Box 21:977)
        - Extension workshops (Box 21:978)
        - Photograph, 1990 (Box 21:979-980)
        - Arrangement and description, 1990 (Box 21:981-982)
        - Outreach, 1990 (Box 21:983)
        - Processing (Box 21:984)
        - Providence workshop (Box 21:985)
        - Caring for Historical Records, 1991 (Box 21:986)
        - Processing, 1991 (Box 21:987)
        - Processing (2nd) (Box 21:988)
        - Evaluations, 1991 (Box 21:989)
        - Workshops, 1992 Spring (Box 21:990)
        - Workshops, 1992 Fall (Box 21:991)
    - Patricia Bodak Stark, 1986-1987
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4:168)
      - SAA Address, 1986 (Box 4:169)
      - President's Files, 1986-1987 (Box 4:170-172)
    - Philip Cronenwett, 1987-1988
      - Annual meeting, 1988 (Box 4:173)
      - Board meeting, 1986 April (Box 4:174)
      - Board meeting, 1986 June (Box 4:175)
      - Board meeting, 1986 October (Box 4:175a)
      - Board meeting, 1987 July (Box 4:176)
      - Board meeting, 1987 October (Box 4:177)
      - Board meeting, 1988 January (Box 4:178)
      - Board meeting, 1988 March (Box 4:179)
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4:180)
      - Meetings, 1986 Fall (Box 4:181)
      - Meetings, 1987 Fall (Box 4:182)
      - Meetings, 1987 Spring (Box 4:183)
      - Meetings, 1988 Spring (Box 4:184)
      - NHPRC, 1988 (Box 4:185)
      - SAA Education Conference, 1987 (Box 4:186)
      - Task Force on Administration, 1987 (Box 4:187)
      - Wilson, Don, 1988 (Box 4:187a)
    - Gregory Sanford, 1988-1989
      - Advisory Board, 1988 (Box 4:188)
      - Board meeting, 1988 October (Box 4:189)
      - Board meeting, 1989 January (Box 4:190)
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 4:191)
      - Current, 1986-1988 (Box 4:192)
      - Haas Award, undated (Box 4:193)
      - Historical Records Workshop--Handouts, undated (Box 5:194)
      - Historical Records Workshop--Materials, 1988 (Box 5:195)
      - Nominating Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5:196)
      - Position descriptions, undated (Box 5:197)
    - Eva Moseley, 1989-1990
      - Board meeting, 1988 July (Box 5:198)
      - Board meeting, 1989 January (Box 5:199)
      - Board meeting, 1989 March (Box 5:200)
      - Board meeting, 1989 June (Box 5:201)
      - Board meeting, 1990 January (Box 5:202)
      - Correspondence, 1989 June - October (Box 5:203)
      - Correspondence, 1990 January - April (Box 5:204)
      - Correspondence--Quill, 1988-1989 (Box 5:205)
      - General, 1980 (Box 23:, Folder 1046)
      - General, 1980-1988 (Box 5:206)
      - Immediate Past President, 1990-1991 (Box 5:297)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 5:208)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5:209)
      - Membership Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 5:210)
      - NEA/MARAC meeting, 1979 (Box 5:211)
      - Nominating Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 5:212)
      - Notes, 1988-1991 (Box 22:1003)
      - Outreach, 1988-1990 (Box 5:213)
      - President's reports, 1989-1990 (Box 5:214)
      - Social Welfare Project, 1988-1992 (Box 5:215)
      - Vice-President, 1987-1989 (Box 5:216)
    - Bruce Stark, 1991-1992
      - Vice president, 1990-1991 (Box 5:217)
      - May, 1991 (Box 5:218)
      - June, 1991 (Box 5:219)
      - July, 1991 (Box 5:220)
      - August, 1991 (Box 5:221)
      - September, 1991 (Box 5:222)
      - October, 1991 (Box 5:223)
      - November, 1991 (Box 5:224)
      - December, 1991 (Box 5:225)
      - January, 1992 (Box 5:226)
      - February, 1992 (Box 5:227)
      - March, 1992 (Box 5:228)
      - April, 1992 (Box 5:229)
    - Megan Sniffin-Marinoff, 1992-1993
      - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 5:230)
      - Fall Meeting, 1992 (Box 5:231)
      - Hale Award, 1992-1993 (Box 5:232)
      - Haas Award, 1993 (Box 5:233)
      - Spring Meeting (20th annual meeting), 1993 (Box 5:234)
      - Nominating Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 5:235)
    - Evelyn M. Cherpak, 1993-1994
      - 3 May - 25 June, 1993 (Box 5:236)
      - 28 June - 15 October, 1993 (Box 5:237)
      - October - January, 1993-1994 (Box 5:238)
      - January - April, 1994 (Box 5:239)
      - 25 June, 1993 (Box 5:240)
    - Gregor Trinkaus-Randall, 1995-1996
      - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 6:241)
    - Christopher Beam, 1996-1997
      - Committee Appointments, 1996-1997 (Box 6:242)
      - Committees: Education, 1996-1997 (Box 6:243)
      - Committees: Haas Award, 1996-1997 (Box 6:244)
      - Committees: Hale Award, 1996-1997 (Box 6:245)
      - Committees: Membership, 1996 (Box 6:246)
      - Committees: Newsletter Editors, 1996 (Box 6:247)
      - Committees: Outreach, 1996 (Box 6:248)
      - Committees: Regional Repository Guide, 1996-1997 (Box 6:249)
      - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 6:250)
      - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 6:251)
      - Dodd Center-NHPRC Application, 1996 (Box 6:252)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 1996 July 12 1996 (Box 6:253)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 1996 October 25 (Box 6:254)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 1997 February 7 (Box 6:255)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 1997 April 25 (Box 6:256)
      - Financial Review, 1996-1997 (Box 6:257)
      - MHRAB NHPRC Application, 1996-1997 (Box 6:258)
      - Meetings: Fall, 1996 (Box 6:259)
      - Meetings: Spring, 1997 (Box 6:260-61)
      - Meetings: Fall, 1997 (Box 6:262)
    - Jean Berry, 1999-2000 (Box 27-28)
      - NEA Archives, 1999, 2005
      - NEA, 2001-
      - Board lists, 1998-2001
      - Board meetings (14 ff), 1998-2001
      - Board correspondence, undated
      - Correspondence, undated
      - Treasurer, undated
      - SAA, 1999
      - Nominating committee (2 ff), 200-2001
      - Distiguished Service award, 200-2001
      - Haas award, 1999
      - Hale award, 1999-2000
      - Cosponsorship, 2000
      - eGroups, 2001
      - Handbook, 2001
      - Job descriptions, 2001
      - Meeting guidelines, undated
      - Membership renewals, 2000
      - Web redesign, 1999-2000
      - Meetings (8 ff), 1999-2002
      - Task force on future directions, 1996
      - Task force on organizational efficiency, 2001
      - Board meetings, 1994-1997
      - Newsletter (2 ff), 1993-1997
    - Joan Krizack, 2002-2003
      - Business meeting, 2003 April 12 (Box 22:1006)
      - Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 22:1004)
      - Financial statements, 2001-2002 (Box 22:1005)
      - Task Force on Fical efficiency, 1996-2001 (Box 22:1007)
    - Rutherford Witthus, 2003-2004
      - Program--Fall meeting, 1998 (Box 22:1010)
      - Meeting--Spring, 2002 (Box 22:1011)
      - Meeting--Fall, 2002 (Box 22:1012)
      - Meeting--Board, 2003 January (Box 22:1013)
      - Meeting--Spring and Summer, 2003 (Box 22:1014)